{
    "subject": "Alan_Rudolph",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Trouble_in_Mind__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Rudolph directed the film Trouble in Mind.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9166199564933777,
            "question": "Who directed the film Trouble in Mind?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883364200592041,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Alan Rudolph."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8591356873512268,
            "question": "Which director made the film Trouble in Mind?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103479146957397,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5837668776512146,
            "question": "What genre is the film Trouble in Mind?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5645354390144348,
            "question": "Who are some actors who appeared in Trouble in Mind?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4436672329902649,
            "question": "Is Trouble in Mind a novel, a play, or a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40505871176719666,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of Trouble in Mind?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.365308552980423,
            "question": "What year was Trouble in Mind released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2933880388736725,
            "question": "What kind of work did Alan Rudolph create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Rudolph directed the film Trouble in Mind.",
            "html": "yago_9761_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Trouble in Mind released?",
            "html": "yago_9761_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the plot of Trouble in Mind?",
            "html": "yago_9761_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Trouble in Mind a novel, a play, or a film?",
            "html": "yago_9761_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9761_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple confirmations that Alan Rudolph directed the film Trouble in Mind. This information is mentioned in various files, including file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9761/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt, 105.txt, and 81.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Alan Rudolph wrote and directed \"Trouble In Mind\" (1985). Therefore, the statement that Alan Rudolph directed the film \"Trouble in Mind\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}